<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<lists>
    <menu>
        <cd><![CDATA[ <i>With a combined experience of nearly 10 years Taylored Beauty aspire to be on trend.<br><br></i><small><font color="grey">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images/image_02.jpg" align="right" style="margin:5px"/>

Katie has worked in most areas within the beauty industry but primarily as a self employed Nail Technician and is renowned locally for her fabulous Bio Sculpture nail creations. Laura specialises in Amazing Eyelash Extensions and has become known for creating the most desired & long lasting lashes in the area. With a successful career in banking Laura has now created such a large client base the beauty has now taken over!
</small></font><br><br>
</i><small><font color="grey">
Both busy working mums with the ability to juggle home life and a passion for 'Tayloring' beauty treatments we aim to offer a relaxed and fashionable service, that no-one else in Alton can provide.
</small></font><br><br>

<b>Message from the Taylor's</b><br><br>
<small><font color="grey"> <i>   We will "Taylor" any beauty need that you have, 
and if a treatment you want is not initially on our list PLEASE ASK! We will endeavour 
to help you. Likewise if you are beauty professional offering a treatment that you would 
like "Taylored" then please get in touch with us as we would be happy to have you in the
salon!</small></font><br><br>   <b> Katie and Laura Taylor</b> <small><font color="grey"> 
Owners </i></small></font> 
        ]]></cd> 
    
        <cd1><![CDATA[   <i>Spray Tanning</i><small><font color="grey">  Using SiennaX and Fake Bake. Long lasting award winning natural looking tans, to suit all skin tones.</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>Bio Sculpture Nails</i><small><font color="grey">  Beautiful Soak off UV Gels lasting 3 weeks before needing infilling. Hottest new colours in stock.</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>Gelish</i><small><font color="grey">  Amazing 14 day Gel Polish.</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>EZ Flow</i><small><font color="grey">  Hard file off gel nails, great for weak and extended nails.</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>HD Brows</i><small><font color="grey">  The celebrity must have of 2012. The 7 step process to fabulous brows. - www.hdbrows.co.uk</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>Amazing Lash Extensions</i><small><font color="grey">  Achieve different looks from natural pretty, to full on glamour with waterproof eyelash extensions. These look great for a holiday or wedding and are lightweight so perfect for everyday.</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>Waxing</i><small><font color="grey">  Using the innovative new wax from Australia, Waxxpress.</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>LVL</i><small><font color="grey">  Lash Volume Length. The perfect way to accentuate your natural lashes.</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>Emani Mineral Make-Up</i><small><font color="grey">  Beautiful soft natural mineral make up by Emani.</small></font>
        ]]></cd1>
        
        <cd2><![CDATA[ <i>Tanning Preparation</i><br><br><small><font color="grey">
            
            Shave/wax at least 24 hours before tanning. Exfoliate, shower and moisturise the night before tanning – do not moisturise on the day of the tan. Remove all face make-up prior to tanning. Wear dark underwear & loose dark clothing. Bring flip flops or loose shoes for after the tanning. Paint nails with clear or coloured nail polish.<br><br>
            
            Not suitable for people with respiratory problems or within the first 3 months of Pregnancy. Any Medical conditions must be disclosed to the therapist, prior to tanning as consent from your G.P. may be required.</small></font><br><br>
            
            <i>Eyelash and Eyebrow Preparation</i><br><br><small><font color="grey">
            
            Patch tests required for Eyelash and Eyebrow Tinting, LVL, and eyelash extensions if extremely sensitive eyes.</small></font><br><br>
            
            
            
            ]]></cd2>
        
        <cd3><![CDATA[
            
            <div class="ui-grid-a">
            <div class="ui-block-a">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//alashes.jpg" width="99%"/>
            </div>
            
            </div>
            <div class="ui-grid-b">
            <div class="ui-block-a">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//lvl.jpg"/>
            </div>
            <div class="ui-block-b">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//HDbrow.jpg"/>
            </div>
            <div class="ui-block-c">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//fakebake.jpg"/>
            </div>
            </div>
            <div class="ui-grid-a">
            <div class="ui-block-a">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//BioSculptureLogo.jpg"/>
            </div>
            <div class="ui-block-b">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//colourcouture.jpg"/>
            </div>
            </div>
            <div class="ui-grid-a">
            <div class="ui-block-a">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//kookygrey.jpg" width="99%"/>
            </div>
            
            </div>
            <div class="ui-grid-a">
            <div class="ui-block-a">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//emani.jpg"/>
            </div>
            <div class="ui-block-b">
            <img src="http://www.mobilefriendlywebapps.co.uk/tayloredtest1/images//gelish.jpg"/>
            </div>
            </div>

            
            ]]></cd3>
        
    </menu>
</lists>